A very good morning friend here box
with another set of questions viewer welcome you to
ask where should rise from mission
possible wireless * otherwise kasana and heavy
arya connected with you is regarding road
safety to make and everyday rumour and secured
no veer vipin question of the day in
studies and screen question child in
on setting on the from you will alauddin
subscribe now to will not allow to
explain why can begin from seed
which alarm to set sh o kinnar or til ki
ab junior with us its aditya
first step to join adho answer is
question and you can win more exciting
prizes they insert youtube and joins page
with your friends and family members and
strong you can also be part of this campaign
and can win more exciting prizes and
exciting things you can participate in
all five questions state 9600 days of this
question in  the UK you already know DR
operation 5 questions in everyone to Andhra inka
kaam and dil shesh mix periods of the
rosaiya road safety and answers questions
and you can participate in all of this and
you can be a part of village school campaign
to to be a part of malik shabd change anar roz
-roz mode setting dikhayo
shukr aashiq why sudhar utsah camp
immigrant ₹100 note employment talking
border road safety rules and say right to
make the road say for everyone you know daily basis
of roads and nobody can request you to be a
part of this and you can now you can bring
change in your driving behaviour
with me to make roads which will not possible
to of everyday important gather follicles to
open the
plant chowk they research school Surya some like it still
beating the animal it is part of the
winner of a daily basis naveen subscribe
and subscribe to this cream
subscribe to see from
Subscribe then you have if he
does it properly you must subscribe to this
business also in from seed you will
not allow him and explain to him
why he cannot sit in the front seat
and allow that edit ok nadia and you will make him
sit in chunari normal book of the
front in India if you
go to foreign countries if you will see
there is absolutely no allowance for children to sit in the
front seat amazon those people
specific there is not enough facility to make your
children sit
and even if they sit then it is very
middle to 9 fashion friend bells important so think they should only bring
change in
new Indian rules where it is very important
for the city of the kids are all family and
inform Arjun that while driving we
must subscribe to do such things which can
distract you away then
you need to be very aware
and driving who is sitting next to you
you should not use any other
screen here  So that your mind is
not disturbed because distraction is the
biggest tree to crush and for that you
can put the lives of not only yourself but also the people around you in danger. If
someone applies the brakes then
you will not have time to react and you will
not be able to apply the brakes. It is very
important to subscribe also.
Focused on road driving 100MB. Now you can show
your knowledge. After that you can increase your
skills and knowledge. I
request you to please subscribe and
subscribe and subscribe till 19 on setting
on the road.
Now what should be done to sit in the front seat,
if he behaves well
or does it properly, he will
ask, if not then will you let him sit in the front
or Allah, choose path SD, absolutely you will let
him sit. Otherwise,
he will start crying.
Drive very fast and explain why he is
not being from the side and you will explain to him.
Now you will not make him sit in the front and you will
explain to him that brother, that is why you want the front seat.
He should not sit on the seat, you will keep giving
him real attention and to get angry at him,
apart from this, by zooming in with the last
salute, you can make him final, it is
not that you cannot take the child forward,
this is something you can use if you
want
and a lot of changes need to be made in our rules and regulations,
to tech
measures, tampering, ring road safety net and
we have seen that people do
not follow the normal rules here, they do not
wear helmets, they do not wear it in the meantime
or you apply hair cream on your cards or while
talking on the phone, friends,
England, Rahu, they do not follow even small things
and it is very important to follow those things so
that we can keep our day
in shape, we can be a part of this campaign
because whatever actions happen on the road, I
agree that we are not responsible for it, but yes,
somewhere or the other we are definitely a partner in it
because at some point or the other we all have broken some
rule or the other, do
those things for ourselves, have
you ever sat alone and thought what mistake
you have made, what wrong you are doing
or when and right click  Or if you are going to drive, have
you ever thought about
what things you should not do because
your carelessness can take someone else's life
or can cause you harm, because of that carelessness
then the person who is following all the things and
doing everything,
you will put his life in danger too or have you seen
that if your vehicle is full of people, if
you are passing by a market or a
school, then a
lot of research is done because there are
children too, there are a lot of
people crossing the road, then whose
responsibility is it, it is the responsibility of all of us, it is the
responsibility of all of us that we should
follow all these rules which are useless
and not for others, not to show off to anyone else,
we
should follow all these Russian regulations for ourselves so
that we can make our day just
for everyone, whether it is a difference on the road, whether it is a bicycle or an
option and riders are
driving a two wheeler, whether Mr. Vinod is driving
or a flower is driving, we are vegetable growers
and  It becomes our responsibility to keep
people and ourselves safe, we can
only make ourselves safe. I request that this is
such a big campaign that
change cannot be brought about by one person alone, so we should
share it with all of you that if we change the things together then
we will be able to implement this thing very soon, so
wearing helmet from the rule regulation became just that, don't drink and
drive to use for my lover point
driving in this is very important, so
somewhere or the other when we change all those things then
somewhere or the other we will be able to make our daily life safe too, so
as you can see
that my present questions are
related to road safety and these are small
daily basis questions which
bother you on daily basis here and
we are applicable somewhere or the other in your daily life,
we bring the same questions related to road safety,
in this you can know what is the correct answer, the
result of the common count world is
our halwa crispy at night  There
is a YouTube in it, they do amount of
dam, this physical exploitation can be done
and you can go there and see the
names of Vinod, who has won in which question
and who has got the tigers, so
many entries are coming, still seeing
everyone participating in this really exciting matter, I
myself am counting the
best part and we have come that together we will
soon be able to make our Russia safe and secure forever
and when we are thinking that we will be able to bring that thing
somewhere, Swami, you
can see on the screen, here the question is Chileshwar,
so this tea is destiny for you, news2 condition on the from
seed of till Ayurveda, a year old child, a
small child, a year old child, you are
requesting from MS Word, you devil 2
Prime, what will
you do, if he sits in the front seat of your car, allauddin
will behave properly, you will turn
off his alarm to sit, if he
behaves properly, ya
Allah, dum to set them and subscribe, now we will let
him sit in the front because otherwise he  We will
start them PM Micro,
don't drive them anymore, that's why you should also listen to
these from seed, you will not alarm him,
now instead of making him sit in the front, you will
explain to him, you will tell him
why we should not sit on Francis,
apart from criticizing others, you will give him a
chair to sit, it's for India
that there is no rule that small children can be made to
sit in the front or not,
between the parents,
tuition, be aware of friends, AIIMS, you
should know what to do, what
not to do for your child, what is enough
and what is not, so now please
join us quickly, you have only 2
hours, after that, Jhal B Bahar and others,
only questions, name system, Viewers Singh
Verma, don't get angry, thank you so much for being a
part of this innovative sitting, to be a
part of this issue and which can affect the
people and Adhir, and thank you so much for
dropping subscribe, definitely subscribe to